let Questions = [
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        "Options": ["Virtual DOM", "Original DOM", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
        "Answer": "Virtual DOM"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is ReactJS?",
        "Options": ["Server-side framework", "User interface framework", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
        "Answer": "User interface framework"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside.",
        "Options": ["Render with arguments", "setState", "PropTypes", "props"],
        "Answer": "props"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who created React.Js?",
        "Options": ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Walke", "Tim Lee", "Jordan Lee"],
        "Answer": "Jordan Walke"
    },
    {
        "Question": "In which language is React.js written?",
        "Options": ["Python", "JavaScript", "Java", "PHP"],
        "Answer": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is Babel?",
        "Options": ["JavaScript compiler", "JavaScript interpreter", "JavaScript transpiler", "None of these"],
        "Answer": "JavaScript compiler"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Identify the command used to create a React app.",
        "Options": ["npm install create-react-app", "npm install –g create-react-app", "install –g create-react-app", "None of the above"],
        "Answer": "npm install –g create-react-app"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
        "Options": ["3000", "3306", "3030", "8080"],
        "Answer": "8080"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How many elements can a valid React component return?",
        "Options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "Answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "Question": "A state in React.js is also known as?",
        "Options": ["The internal storage of the component", "External storage of the component", "Permanent storage", "All of the above"],
        "Answer": "The internal storage of the component"
    }
    
]

export default Questions;